# **DEVON LEDUFF**

(678) 481-2747 | devonleduff@gmail.com

## **Professional Summary:**

An Army National Guard member trained as an 35T Military Intelligence Systems Maintainer/Integrator who is an accomplished Systems Administrator. I Have over four years of experience providing technical solutions through high-quality service and support. Seeking a position in a challenging and rewarding tech environment where I can expand upon my existing skill base while contributing to a lively IT team.

Security Clearance: Active TS/SCI w/ CI Poly

## **Skills:**

- IT security best practices
- Interpersonal Skills
- Team player
- Windows 7, Windows 10
- Windows Server 2008
- Microsoft Office
- Large Computer Networks
- Documentation
- Red Hat Linux
- Kvm Virtualization
- Microsoft USMT
- LDAP

- Active Directory
- Oracle Database
- DSCG-A
- VMSphere
- Vmotion
- SNMP
- Chef
- Bash scripting
- Jira

## **Certifications:**

- CompTIA Security+ Certified
- CompTIA Network+ Certified

# **Work History:**

### **Cloud System Administrator**

Insight Global Richardson, Texas

Aug 2019 - Jan 2020

- The primary responsibility is to work in coordination with the IT department to develop and support cloud, windows and Linux infrastructure. provide technical assistance on windows, cloud-based systems, and resolve operational problems.
- Approve change requests associated with modifications to cloud resource
- View pending approvals for cloud resources
- View and analyze summary data on cloud resource deployments
- Monitor reguests and key metrics for cloud resources
- Install and configure the Cloud Management application for the provider (for example, AWS, Azure, or VMware)
- Set properties for Cloud Management
- Run Discovery on the cloud resources
- Obtain templates and approve some templates to be used to create catalog items
- Define catalog items for both VMs and more complex offerings
- Configure default lease settings

- Set pricing for the catalog items
- Define and activate provisioning rules
- Define and activate tagging rules
- Define change control parameters for cloud resources
- Customize the user experience: Provisioning rules and UI policies
- Define the schedule for downloading billing data

### **Linux Field Engineer**

Alku via Leidos Tyson Center, Virgina

Oct 2018 - June 2019

- Automate standardized steps, perform scripts, and complete instructions lists, provide sophisticated
  monitoring and troubleshooting for Linux-based servers that are virtualized, use troubleshooting
  procedures and technical information to identify severity of incidents and carry out accordingly the
  resolution process, research issues that do not have a recognized solution and prepare a resolution
  process for them, partner with developers to create strong software products, and write and maintain
  scripts, such as python and shell, that automate tech operations.
- Assist in tweaking the performance of the system, so that network infrastructure is abundantly
  available. Responsible for the development and maintenance of configuration management solutions.
  provide support for infrastructure, design and develop tools for infrastructure monitoring and reporting.
- Implement better security practices across an organization's applications and deploy solutions to enhance productivity.
- Configure and maintain Oracle Databases with PostgreSQL.
- Configure, install and Manage Window-based workstations
- Upgrading Computer Software and Hardware
- Email, Remote, Phone, and Video Customer support (over 20 different countries)
- Customer Service and Customer relations
- Installation of Linux based servers and window workstations
- General Management of Databases with PostgreSQL
- Manage Network equipment (Switches and Routers) connectivity
- Troubleshooting with Virtualization (VSphere)

#### **Electronic Technician II**

Jan 2018 - Sept 2018

GENESIS via Dyncorp International Fort Shafter, Hawaii

- Applies advanced technical knowledge to fault isolation, scheduling and maintaining complex communications and electronics systems in accordance with customer standards
- Develops integration plans and performs hardware integrations, and manages documentation schematics and modifications
- Configures computer communications devices, and peripheral equipment to operate within designated networks
- Designs and plans for and executes network hardware installation, testing, and validation.
- Prepares, maintains equipment, configuration documentation, and performs physical configuration audits
- Basic Python
- Basic Machine learning and Deep Learning Algorithms

#### Installation Technician/Shift Lead Technician

Sept 2017 – Jan 2018

Camp Lejeune, North Carolina

- Installed Microsoft operating systems (Win-10) and applications included in the Microsoft Office Professional suite along with other software applications and hardware
- Experienced in a production environment
- Experienced in a leadership role
- Setup and installed/image EUD (End User Device), transfer data, map printers and drives
- Oversaw the installation, and transition of the MCEDS (Marine Corps Enterprise Desktop System) WIN10 SHB (Secure Host Baseline)

# Military Intelligence Systems Maintainer/Integrator (35Y) May 2016 – Aug 2017

US Army - 305th Military Intelligence BN, Alpha Company: Fort Huachuca

- Successfully completed practical training in the fields of computer networking, computer security, CISCO routers and switches, Windows systems integration/administration, Linux systems integration/administration, DCGS-A(v3.2.4.4) systems integration/administration, computer engineering, radio frequency transmission, digital receiver's technology, and electrical engineering
- Evaluated and conducted technical and functional research and analysis
- Configured, integrated and troubleshooted Windows and Linux Redhat servers and workstations to 100% operability within a network using Active Directory
- Used Access Control Lists to configure, integrate and troubleshoot CISCO routers and switches within a WAN and LAN
- Conducted network vulnerability assessments using tools to evaluate attack vectors, identify system vulnerabilities and develop remediation plans and security procedures
- Wrote accurate reports detailing the different network vulnerabilities identified and corrected during troubleshooting exercises
- Assembled a fully functional computer and troubleshoot computer hardware errors

#### Forklift Operator/Inventory Manager

Mar 2016 – May 2016

Home Depot Direct Fulfillment Distribution Center – 2400 Georgia 155 South, Locust Grove, GA 30248

## **Forklift Operator**

May 2015 - Oct 2015

Select Staffing

- Maintained equipment in good working order by checking fluid levels and greasing and fueling machines
- Immediately communicated any equipment issues to the supervisor
- Kept efficient time and material records
- Planned all lifts and used capacity charts

### **Education:**

**Luella High School** - 603 Walker Drive Locust Grove GA Graduated 2014

Some College Taken:

Georgia Southern University - 1332 Southern Dr, Statesboro, GA 30458

Associate of Applied Science: Network Technology Current

Cochise College - Sierra Vista AZ

## **Personal Reference:**

Lead Tech in HI- Jerrad (618)795-4200

Lead Tech in NC -Jermaine (912) 532-9771

Supervisor in VA - Kevin (703)-887-7074